Duplicate Slug Found: indonesia_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 10 - Indonesia Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 18 - Indonesia Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: thailand_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 11 - Thailand Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 21 - Thailand Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: abu_dhabi_securities_exchange
  Index 1: 13 - Abu Dhabi Securities Exchange
  Index 2: 25 - Abu Dhabi Securities Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: borsa_italiana
  Index 1: 51 - Borsa Italiana
  Index 2: 78 - Borsa Italiana
Duplicate Slug Found: kazakhstan_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 22 - Kazakhstan Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 84 - Kazakhstan Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: mexican_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 101 - Mexican Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 114 - Mexican Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: jamaica_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 102 - Jamaica Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 116 - Jamaica Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: bermuda_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 103 - Bermuda Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 117 - Bermuda Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: botswana_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 139 - Botswana Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 156 - Botswana Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: zambia_securities_exchange
  Index 1: 142 - Zambia Securities Exchange
  Index 2: 158 - Zambia Securities Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: zimbabwe_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 140 - Zimbabwe Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 159 - Zimbabwe Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: victoria_falls_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 141 - Victoria Falls Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 160 - Victoria Falls Stock Exchange
Duplicate Slug Found: malawi_stock_exchange
  Index 1: 143 - Malawi Stock Exchange
  Index 2: 161 - Malawi Stock Exchange
